<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vidhance</title>
    <link>http://vidhance.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Vidhance</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://vidhance.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://vidhance.com/start/start/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vidhance.com/start/start/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Vidhance provides software solutions for real-time video enhancement and analysis, supporting human perception of time-critical events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our products use the efficient Vidhance live video enhancement technology, with capabilities such as:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rotational and planar video stabilization&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scene adaptive contrast optimization&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Real-time image mosaicking&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Object tracking&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colorization&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://vidhance.com/careers/jobApplication/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vidhance.com/careers/jobApplication/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://vidhance.com/careers/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vidhance.com/careers/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;about-imint:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;About Imint&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imint is a small high-tech software startup, located at Uppsala. The company has its roots in the Center for Image Analysis at Uppsala University. Initially, the company focused on enhancing live aerial surveillance video streams by removing obstacles for human perception, caused by vibration, turbulence, bad weather, etc. Today, Imint is serving a broad range of customers in a variety of fields. Whenever time critical decisions, based on video sources are made, Imint&amp;rsquo;s technology can come into play.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;engineering-candidate-profile:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;Engineering Candidate Profile&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to specific demands for individual positions, we believe a candidate to our engineering team should match these requirements:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Genuine interest in software development; assiduous and with high quality standards&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unprestigious and willing to discuss, learn and teach&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enjoying being a team player with involvement in all aspects of our business&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interest in interacting with customers and partners, including travelling abroad&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Education level MSc or equivalent&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English and at least with functional Swedish&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;working-at-imint:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;Working at Imint&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At Imint, we are software professionals. We develop innovative technology in the areas of video enhancement and video analytics for the most demanding situations. As a small team, we need to be both versatile and agile, with short cycles from idea, to proof-of-concept and further on to mature field deployed solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since Imint is an entrepreneurial and fast growing technology company, we appreciate dynamic, self-propelled and all-round talented co-workers with good social and communication skills, who thrive in a start-up corporate culture. We value sincerity and responsibility, and those who can combine creativity with ability to plan and deliver. Working with us should be both challenging and fun, we are driven by vision, and we appreciate a culture where good ideas and ability to execute, rather than titles, count.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Working at Imint is and shall be challenging. Our international customers and partners put high expectations on us and our capabilities. To thrive with us, you should feel energized by such demands.To be able to excel in a demanding and dynamic environment, balance in life is a key component. To ensure enduring creativity, passion and commitment when working in our team, there must be sufficient time outside of the job. Imint values differences in experience, background, and opinions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Apply to any of our positions described below by filling out &lt;a href=&#34;http://vidhance.com/careers/jobApplication/&#34;&gt;this form&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://vidhance.com/info/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vidhance.com/info/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;from-eyes-in-the-sky:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;From Eyes in the Sky&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imint was founded in 2007, based on research at Uppsala University, Center for Image Analysis. Initially, the company focused on enhancing live aerial surveillance video streams by removing obstacles for human perception;caused by disturbances, such as uncontrollable movements, vibration and turbulence, and caused by low contrast visibility, caused by fog, mist and rain. The resulting core software package is Vidhance®.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2009, Imint introduced the rapid video analysis tool Ihvert® to increase ISR capabilities in unmanned aerial systems (UAS). Since then, the aerial reconnaissance market has continued to be an important arena for Imint.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, Imint is serving a broader range of customers in a variety of fields, with new products. Focus has remained on Vidhance, which is constantly improved and expanded in functionality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whenever time critical decisions are made, based on video sources, Imint has the software technology fit for the purpose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;contact-info-contact:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://vidhance.com/info/contact&#34;&gt;Contact&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;address:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;Address&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imint AB&lt;br /&gt;
S:t Larsgatan 5&lt;br /&gt;
753 11 Uppsala&lt;br /&gt;
Sweden&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;phone:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;Phone&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;+46 18 4749990&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;e-mail:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;E-Mail&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:info@imint.se&#34;&gt;info@imint.se&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://vidhance.com/start/stabilizationvideo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vidhance.com/start/stabilizationvideo/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://vidhance.com/start/quote/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vidhance.com/start/quote/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;It’s worth noting that Sweden-based Imint isn’t some fly-by-night startup. The company has been writing and selling image stabilization and analysis software for military drones since 2007. [...] - the company recently decided that it could  probably use the tricks it learned from that work (and the patents it got for it) to bring these capabilities to smartphones, too.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;cite&gt;Frederic Lardinois, TechCrunch, January 2015&lt;/cite&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://vidhance.com/info/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vidhance.com/info/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The easiest way to contact us is to fill out the form below.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Battle-proven</title>
      <link>http://vidhance.com/start/battleprovenImage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vidhance.com/start/battleprovenImage/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solutions</title>
      <link>http://vidhance.com/start/solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vidhance.com/start/solutions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Vidhance® technology is a modular and highly optimized suite of filters, algorithms, and analytic functions for real-time processing of live video streams. It brings capabilities to a standard computer unit that would otherwise need dedicated hardware.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is used to enhance full motion video from both moving and fixed cameras and is used in products ranging from unmanned aircrafts and ground vehicles to portable consumer devices.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://vidhance.com/start/solConsumerDevice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vidhance.com/start/solConsumerDevice/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;portable-consumer-devices:05cb9fdf88133533bebfd2e76746a4ee&#34;&gt;Portable Consumer Devices&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The smartphone market has seen a technology race in terms of camera performance, and market leading devices are now capable of near-professional still photography. Video performance and quality were left behind in this race, but the Vidhance® software platform will enable video to make a leap in the same direction as still photography.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://vidhance.com/start/solAerialSurveillance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vidhance.com/start/solAerialSurveillance/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;aerial-surveillance-and-uas:bf713acae3df02e11acd15284628f8b6&#34;&gt;Aerial Surveillance and UAS&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Video from unmanned aerial systems can often be affected by disturbances such as uncontrollable movements, vibration, weather conditions, and more. The Vidhance® technology addresses this kind of issues and provides improved video to the viewer inside a ground control station or remote video terminal in real-time.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://vidhance.com/start/solAirTrafficMgmnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vidhance.com/start/solAirTrafficMgmnt/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;air-traffic-management:2415efa5a2bfc3d1b8a85ee605c31b3c&#34;&gt;Air Traffic Management&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Air traffic control is more reliant on video than ever, and airports see more and more cameras being installed not only for traffic control, but also for security and perimeter protection purposes. However, weather and video visibility are not always favorable. Vidhance® improves the video feed received at the remote traffic control by addressing weather effects such as fog, mist, uneven illumination etc. It also provides object tracking and other video analytic functions.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://vidhance.com/start/solGroundVehicles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vidhance.com/start/solGroundVehicles/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;ground-vehicles-ugvs-and-robots:f50512564ba9a63c628e1fa9189abc32&#34;&gt;Ground Vehicles, UGVs and Robots&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remote controlled robots or unmanned ground vehicles used on missions such as bomb defusal or search and rescue will have problems with visual disturbances affecting the video feed. Vidhance® improves the video where weather conditions, smoke, vibrations, and artificial illumination etc. impair visibility, and makes it easier for the operator to reduce the risk of missing crucial details.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://vidhance.com/start/solUnderwaterRobots/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vidhance.com/start/solUnderwaterRobots/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;underwater-and-sub-surface-video:e242e8c59b58ace45695a96d315f3583&#34;&gt;Underwater and Sub-Surface Video&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remote controlled underwater robots have become an essential tool in various deep sea operations. Vidhance® can reduce the effects of uneven illumination and improve visibility in murky waters by applying contrast optimization.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior utvecklare/produktledare inom video</title>
      <link>http://vidhance.com/careers/positions/seniorEngineer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://vidhance.com/careers/positions/seniorEngineer/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;uppsala-sweden:7d4aa3e758f48a49792baab6ea6f6ec2&#34;&gt;Uppsala, Sweden&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re looking for candidates with a functional level of Swedish. As a consequence, this position is described in Swedish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;om-imint:7d4aa3e758f48a49792baab6ea6f6ec2&#34;&gt;Om Imint&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imint AB är ett mjukvarubolag med kontor i Uppsala. Företaget har sitt ursprung i forskning vid Centrum för bildanalys vid Uppsala universitet. Från början fokuserade vi på att förbättra video från förarlösa flygplan, för att reducera sådant som stör mänsklig varseblivning, som till exempel vibrationer och dålig sikt. Utvecklingen fortsatte mot andra realtidsvideotillämpningar, som t.ex. fjärrstyrda fordon och maskiner och olika typer av spaningssytem. Idag har vi på Imint utvecklat vår unika och patenterade mjukvara vidare för konsumentelektroni i produktfamiljen Vidhance® Mobile, och vi arbetar med kunder över hela världen som till exempel välkända smartphone-tillverkare. År 2014 såldes mer än en miljard smarta telefoner, och vår ambition är att förbättra användarupplevelsen av videoinspelning för denna enorma marknad. Nu expanderar vi kraftigt, för att möta ett mycket starkt intresse för vår teknik. Webtidningen TechCrunch skrev nyligen om Imint i den &lt;a href=&#34;http://techcrunch.com/2015/01/09/imint-wants-to-bring-real-time-video-stabilization-to-android/&#34;&gt;här artikeln&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;att-jobba-hos-oss:7d4aa3e758f48a49792baab6ea6f6ec2&#34;&gt;Att jobba hos oss&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vi är mjukvaruexperter och algoritmutvecklare. Vi bygger innovativ teknik inom videoförbättring och videoanalys för krävande tillämpningar och med hårda realtidskrav. Vi är ett mindre team men i snabb tillväxt, och vi behöver vara både mångkunniga och flexibla. Vi jobbar med korta cykler från idé vidare till koncept och leverans ut till kund, och är inspirerade av Lean Startup-rörelsen. Hur ser morgondagens användande av mobil video ut - och vilka behov kan vår produkt fylla?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vi har en entreprenörskultur. Det innebär att de som är initiativrika och självgående problemlösare trivs bäst hos oss. Vi uppskattar ärlighet och ansvarstagande, och förmågan att både vara kreativ och kunna planera och genomföra. Det skall vara både krävande och roligt att jobba hos oss, och våra internationella kunder och partner har höga förväntningar. Det är viktigare med vad du tillför i idéer och handlingar, än din bakgrund och dina formella meriter. För att kunna leverera bra resultat krävs balans i livet. Tid måste finnas för annat än jobb för att kreativitet och passion skall få uthålligt utrymme. Vi har en kultur av ömsesidighet, där vi ger bra förutsättningar att få ihop både arbets- och familjeliv. Vi uppskattar olikheter; i bakgrund, erfarenheter och åsikter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;arbetsbeskrivning:7d4aa3e758f48a49792baab6ea6f6ec2&#34;&gt;Arbetsbeskrivning:&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hos Imint finns inga tydliga avdelningar och hårt ritade gränser. Vår uppgift är att omsätta innovativa idéer och forskningsnära kunskap till riktiga funktioner i var mans hand, och på kort tid. Denna roll har dock fokus på levererbara produkter och kundintegration. Imints mjukvara Vidhance Mobile integreras som mjukvarukomponenter direkt i kundens produkt (som till exempel en smartphone), och som en utökning till operativsystemets abstraktionslager för kamerahårdvara. I dagsläget stöds Android, men andra operativsystem kan komma. För denna roll värdesätts kvalitetsmedvetenhet, erfarenhet av metoder för systematisk testning och kvalitetskontroll, och principer för effektivt produktunderhåll - i korthet erfarenhet av produktvård och produktledning för mjukvara.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;kvalifikationer:7d4aa3e758f48a49792baab6ea6f6ec2&#34;&gt;Kvalifikationer:&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;generella-meriter-ingenjör-hos-imint:7d4aa3e758f48a49792baab6ea6f6ec2&#34;&gt;Generella meriter - ingenjör hos Imint&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Förutom specifika krav på enskilda tjänster, så söker vi huvudsakligen de med följande meriter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Geniunt intresse för mjukvaruutveckling, och med hög ambitionsnivå.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prestigelös attityd, och öppen för att lära och lära ut.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lagspelare som uppskattar att vara involverad i all vår verksamhet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kundinriktad, uppskattar att kommunicera med kunder och partners, och ibland resa utomlands.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Utbildningsnivå civilingenjör eller motsvarande.&lt;br /&gt;
-Talar flytande och skriver god engelska. Funktionell nivå på svenska. Ytterligare språkkunskaper är meriterande, till exempel östasiatiska språk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;rollen:7d4aa3e758f48a49792baab6ea6f6ec2&#34;&gt;Rollen&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vi söker en senior mjukvaruutvecklare och/eller produktledare med följande kvalifikationer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ års arbetserfarenhet, varav flera års erfarenhet av kommersiell mjukvaruutveckling och produkthantering.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stor skicklighet i att programmera i  C, C# eller Java.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;God erfarenhet av modern test- och utvecklingsmetodik inom mjukvara.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;God erfarenhet av att hantera produktcykeln för mjukvara; från utrullning till produktvård och underhåll och uppdateringar.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Erfarenhet av att förtroendefullt arbeta med kunder i en produkt- eller leveransorganisation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;ytterligare-meriter:7d4aa3e758f48a49792baab6ea6f6ec2&#34;&gt;Ytterligare meriter&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I listan nedan anger vi några punkter där sökande kan hitta en &amp;ldquo;spets&amp;rdquo;, och rekommenderas att lyfta fram sådant i en ansökan. Punkterna utgör dock inte hårda krav.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Erfarenhet av mjukvara för videotillämpningar, tex. erfarenhet av DirectShow, GStreamer eller Media Foundation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Erfarenhet och intresse av bildbehandling eller videoanalys, med erfarenhet av verktyg som till exempel OpenCV.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Erfarenhet av OpenGL och/eller OpenGL-ES och utveckling och optimering av shaders.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Goda kunskaper inom datorvetenskap och datorarkitektur.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Erfarenhet med goda vitsord från att leda projekt eller team i en produktorganisation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Erfarenhet av att utveckla på Android, på operativsystems- eller drivrutinsnivå, och erfarenhet av att utveckla på inbyggnadsdatorer med hög prestanda, som till exempel ARM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Erfarenhet av att utveckla algoritmer i mjukvara med hårda realtidskrav, gärna i multitrådade processer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bra förståelse för digital kamerateknik och Image Signal Processesing (ISP).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Personligt intresse av fotografi/videografi, datorgrafik, optik/kamerateknik, eller liknande&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kvalitetsmedveten och med bra prioriteringsförmåga under stressiga perioder, och som skapar förtroende hos medarbetare och kunder.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;villkor:7d4aa3e758f48a49792baab6ea6f6ec2&#34;&gt;Villkor:&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imint erbjuder rätt sökande en marknadsmässig lön, med kollektivavtalshärmande villkor. Vi tillämpar flexibel arbetstid inom ramen för kärntid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;processen:7d4aa3e758f48a49792baab6ea6f6ec2&#34;&gt;Processen:&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I den tillväxtfas som Imint är inne i, sker rekrytering löpande. Vi uppmanar dock att söka tjänsten senast den 30 augusti 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vi ber i första hand kandidater att använda vårt &lt;a href=&#34;http://vidhance.com/careers/jobApplication/&#34;&gt;webformulär&lt;/a&gt; vid ansökningar. Vi ber också att frågor om tjänsten eller rekryteringsprocessen i första hand ställs per email till &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:careers@imint.se&#34;&gt;careers@imint.se&lt;/a&gt;, eftersom rekryterande chefer ofta är på resande fot i andra tidszoner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;viktig-info-till-rekryteringsfirmor-important-note-to-firms:7d4aa3e758f48a49792baab6ea6f6ec2&#34;&gt;Viktig info till rekryteringsfirmor : Important note to firms:&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vi önskar ej bli kontaktade av rekryterings- eller outplacementföretag, utan enbart av ansökande individer. &lt;em&gt;Note: No firm solicitation&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>